legallyindia.com 2010-12-02

# Privacy policy | Legally India

##  Privacy policy

Written by KG   | 

We are committed to protecting your privacy and we will do what we reasonably can to protect the identity and private details of all users on this site.

  1. Please note that if you are registered, your username, profession and location you provide will be visible to other users of the site.
  2. You can change your personal details at any time by logging into the Website and going to the Community – Your profile menu.
  3. Any comments submitted to the Website or posts made via our forums are readable by the public so please think before you post under your real name.
  4. If you prefer writing a comment on a story anonymously, please log out of your account and comment as an unregistered guest.
  5. We reserve the right to personally contact you via the email address you provide at any time, including but not limited to when commenting, posting in forums, getting in touch over the contact forms on our page. However, we will at all times keep your identity and email address confidential, subject to this privacy policy and the terms and conditions.

  6. In order to improve our website we may collect, store and use your personal data, such as:   
(i)information about your computer, your IP address and your use of this website;   
(ii)the information that you provided when you registered with us and/or our newsletters; and  
(iii) any other information that you choose to send to us.
  7. We will take reasonable care and adopt security precautions to safeguard your personal data and prevent its loss and misuse. However, we can not guarantee the security or privacy of information or data sent over internet connections, even if encrypted.
  8. If you have subscribed to our email newsletter we may contact you by email to send you the newsletters. 
  9. If you are not subscribed to our email newsletter we may get in touch very rarely by email if there is a major issue that needs your attention, concerning security, privacy or anything else that is important.
  10. We will not share your personal information with third parties without your permission or unless: (i) our ownership changes or we merge or enter into a joint-venture with another party, (ii) we are required to do so by law, or (iii) in connection with any legal proceedings and/or to defend our legal rights.
  11. We may transfer any information we store and use between any of the countries in which we operate in order to assist us in providing our website and our services.
  12. We may use your personal information for advertising, marketing and public relations for our own business and we are committed to complying with the UK’s Data Protection Act 1998 and its eight principles.
  13. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
  14. We can change this privacy policy at any time but we will always notify you or give you the option of opting out if the new policy results in a fundamentally different use of the information from its use under the current policy.

Comments (0)

 **NB: By clicking and/or reading the below comments you agree that you do so at your own risk.** _Comments are the personal views and opinions expressed by readers and are not those of Legally India. Because anonymous comments may be biased or unreliable, you agree that you will not allow any comment(s) to affect your view of the reputation of any person(s) or organisation(s). If you believe a comment is inappropriate, please[send us a message](http://www.legallyindia.com/contact) with your objection and contact details and we will review it as soon as practicable._

Write comment
